{
    "id": "0e49844d5cc8412eb464f96e9d5fcc7a",
    "title": "Words Followed By Particular Prepositions",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "One must never deviate ……………….. the right path.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "to",
                "with",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9ef2087d8778427cb2d09f5daf86a4bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Eventually she acceded ……………….. my requests.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c5552902cdcc4e2d8b858bf33c48dba1"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no cure ...................... many forms of cancer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "for",
                "against"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0c1ca8b9640d4797ad31a4a9eef3c710"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is keen ………………….. pursuing higher education in the US.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "at",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "363abc9cce024ebfb1e5e871fd61c0dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "His latest novels make several allusions …………………. Hindu Mythology.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "42a40b5f6df54f1c8af27e5422b28938"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was anxious .....................… contact his parents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "about",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b73ed9e89fa74f8e85815f325d01b7f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has an aptitude ………………… music.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3aa678aa390e46bfaab4a9463632fcd1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The indulgent mother is always blind …………………. her child’s faults.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c4627dd85eb948e4bab964c28c921c7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was brought ……………….. by his grandparents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "up",
                "over",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "79930aa929f84aaaa20cca38ef5061d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is addicted …………………. drinking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "from",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5ac2d9efa6664859853b947bacf29b92"
        }
    ]
}